https://animadomus.com/privacy/

Wish List 0PrivacyPrivacy PolicyAnima Domus does not collect personal information about individual users except when such personal information is provided to Anima Domus on a voluntary basis. The individual’s personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user, except that Anima Domus reserves the right to disclose such personal information: (a) to its affiliates, subsidiaries and third party agents for purposes related to providing services associated with the Site; or (b) if such disclosure is made pursuant to a requirement or request of a government agency, subpoena or other legal proceeding or otherwise required by lawPlease note that certain services associated with the Site may not be available to you in the event that you choose not to provide personal information.Users should also be aware that through the use of “cookies”, non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Anima Domus’s Internet servers.“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are gathered by browsing on websites to: (a) recognize repeat users; (b) track usage behavior; and (c) compile aggregate data that will permit content improvements. Users should be aware that Anima Domus cannot control or prevent the use of cookies or any information obtained through such cookies by third parties. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers permit the user to disable the cookie feature. However, users are advised that cookies may be required for the use of certain features on the Site.Join our VIP ListEmail* EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Get social! Facebook Instagram Houzz Pinterest YoutubeTop
